(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-19T02:30:50.234908",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
なんであなたにはできないの なんてさ
“Why can't you do it?” they say.
陰口言われたり 呆れられたり 口角下がる everyday
Being gossiped about, being despaired of, corners of my mouth dropping every day.
電車は私を置き去りにしちゃうし
The train leaves me behind,
葉物野菜もスピード早すぎだね
and leafy vegetables spoil too quickly.
ありのままの私だけじゃ足りないんだ fight with me
Just being my raw self isn't enough, fight with me.
毎日死ぬほど頑張ってやっとここまで連れてきたんだ
I worked to death every day to finally bring myself this far.
あなたにはわからない
You don't understand,
分かってほしくない
and I don't want you to understand.
私の苦労も苦しみもご存知ないでいてね
Please stay completely oblivious to my struggles and my pain.
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a moment for the performance to begin.
きっとあなたにもできるはず なんてさ
“I'm sure you can do it too,” they say.
言うほど無責任にはなりたくない
I don't want to be as irresponsible as those words.
それでも死ぬほど頑張って賭ける価値はあると思った
Even so, I thought it was worth betting on by working to death.
投げ出したくなるよ
I feel like throwing it all away,
でも諦めたくはない
but I don't want to give up.
私の未来も失敗も全部私だけのもの
My future and my failures are all mine alone.
あなたにはわからない
You don't understand,
分かってほしくない
and I don't want you to understand.
私の苦労も苦しみもご存知ないで
Stay completely oblivious to my struggles and my pain.
投げ出したくなるよ
I feel like throwing it all away,
でも諦めたくはない
but I don't want to give up.
私の未来も失敗も全部渡さないよ
I won't hand over my future or my failures to anyone.
気づかない 気づかないでいて
Don't notice, please stay unaware.
可愛いだけの私でいい
It's fine if I'm just cute.
アイスみたいに
Just like ice cream,
とろけてわかんなくなる
melting away and confusing me.
夢も愛もぎゅっとしていっぱいだから
My dreams and love are squeezed so full,
もうちぎれない
they won't ever break.
でも欲張りすぎて きっと落ちていく
But being too greedy, I'll surely fall down.
もうらくらくちゅっちゅ 恋に落ちちゃって
Already easy-peasy chu-chu, falling in love,
きゅっきゅ 戻れない
kyu-kyu, there's no turning back.
あれあれなんで ふわりと心が まだ熱くなるの
Oh my, why does my fluttering heart still burn so hot?
もうらくらくちゅっちゅ 君の重力で
Already easy-peasy chu-chu, drawn by your gravity,
きゅっきゅ 引き寄せて
kyu-kyu, pull me closer.
カレイドスコープ覗いてるみたいで ねえ
It's like looking through a kaleidoscope, hey...
キラキラな未来みたい わからない
I want to see a sparkling future, but I don't know.
あぁ アップアンドダウンで超振り回す
Ah, tossing me around so much with ups and downs,
YOU & I todayを四六時中
you and I, all day long.
カレンダー32日でも足りない
Even a 32-day calendar wouldn't be enough.
あれもこれもそれも全部したい
I want to do this, that, and everything!
きゅんきゅんきゅん上昇 どきどき拍手
Kyun-kyun-kyun rising, pounding heart, applause!
きゅんきゅんきゅん下降 深呼吸
Kyun-kyun-kyun falling, deep breath.
きゅんきゅんきゅん上昇 ラブラブメーター
Kyun-kyun-kyun rising, lovey-dovey meter!
きゅんきゅんきゅん降下 突然ギュー！
Kyun-kyun-kyun falling, sudden tight hug!
無限大の間クラッシュ 失敗だけど諦めない
Clashing in the midst of infinity, it's a failure but I won't give up.
まだ欲張りだから 君と落ちていく
Because I'm still greedy, I'm falling with you.
もうらくらくちゅっちゅ 心が絡まって
Already easy-peasy chu-chu, our hearts are intertwined,
きゅっきゅ 抜け出せない
kyu-kyu, I can't escape.
あれあれなんで 目まぐるしい心が まだ熱くなるの
Oh my, why does my dizzy heart still burn so hot?
もうらくらくちゅっちゅ スピード重視で
Already easy-peasy chu-chu, prioritizing speed,
きゅっきゅ 引き寄せて
kyu-kyu, pull me closer.
カレイドスコープ覗いてるみたいで ねえ
It's like looking through a kaleidoscope, hey...
キラキラな未来みたい わからない
I want to see a sparkling future, but I don't know.
バーチャル？リアル？どっちかわいい？
Virtual? Real? Which one is cute?
バーチャル！リアル！どっちもかわいい！
Virtual! Real! Both are cute!
check it ちゅ きちゅき ちゅるっ chu
Check it, chu, ki-chu-ki, churuttu chu!
チェリ チェリー チューイン チュ イン ちょ
Cheri, cherry, chewing, chu-in, cho!
サムネ タップ はじめまして
Tapping the thumbnail, nice to meet you!
きゅんきゅんってしたなら ハート押して
If it made your heart skip, press that heart button!
通知は on いつでも come on
Turn on notifications, come on anytime!
一緒に踊ろうよ on and on
Let's dance together, on and on!
お菓子食べたいけどダイエット中
I want to eat sweets, but I'm on a diet...
キミの好みにアップデート中
Updating myself to match your taste!
ポチり更新 キミと交信
Click to update, communicating with you,
もっと推してほしいの
I want you to support me even more!
「バーチャル？リアル？どっちが好き？」
"Virtual? Real? Which one do you like?"
繋がる 1 2 3次元
Connecting the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd dimensions,
ワン トゥー スリーで飛び越えて
jumping across with a one, two, three!
今やネットもリアルです
Now, even the internet is real.
チクチクしないで ラブとピースで
No need for stinging words, just love and peace!
ときめいちゃう 時かけ girl
A heart-throbbing time-traveling girl...
混ぜれば 最強
mixed together, we are the strongest!
バーチャリアラブ
Virtu-Real Love!
check it ちゅ きちゅき ちゅるっ chu
Check it, chu, ki-chu-ki, churuttu chu!
チェリ チェリー チューイン チュ イン ちょ
Cheri, cherry, chewing, chu-in, cho!
2番にスワイプ beat足して
Swipe to the second verse, add a beat,
きゅんきゅんってしたなら 手叩いて
if it made your heart skip, clap your hands!
ガチ勢もエンジョイ勢も
Both hardcore fans and casual enjoyers,
一緒に踊ろうよ on and on
let's dance together, on and on!
界隈ちがうけどコラボ中
We're from different circles, but we're collaborating!
new楽しいことリサーチ中
Researching brand-new fun things!
ぴぴぴテレパシー今日も配信
Pi-pi-pi telepathy, streaming today too,
もっとハート欲しいの
I want even more hearts!
ねえ ねえ
Hey, hey,
どっちかわいい？
which is cute?
どっちカワイイ？
Which is cute?
どっち可愛い？
どっちかわいい？
Which is cute?
どっちカワイイ？
どっち可愛い？
Which is cute?
ねえ ねえ
Hey, hey,
どっちかわいい？
which is cute?
どっちカワイイ？
Which is cute?
どっち可愛い？
どっちかわいい？
Which is cute?
どっちカワイイ？
どっち可愛い？
Which is cute?
どっちも kawaii
Both are kawaii!
お菓子食べたいけどダイエット中
I want to eat sweets, but I'm on a diet...
キミの好みにアップデート中
Updating myself to match your taste!
ポチり更新 キミと交信
Click to update, communicating with you,
もっと推してほしいの
I want you to support me even more!
「バーチャル？リアル？どっちが好き？」
"Virtual? Real? Which one do you like?"
「バーチャル？リアル？どっちも好き」
"Virtual? Real? I love both!"
いつだって 1・2・3次元
Always in 1, 2, 3 dimensions...
1・2・3で飛び越えて
Leaping over with 1, 2, 3!
今やネットもリアルで
Now the internet is real too.
ギクシャクしないでラブ＆ピース
Don't be awkward, love and peace!
キミとボクは wow wow
You and I are, wow wow...
ときめきちょっと 研ぎ澄まして
Sharpening our excitement a little...
2D 3D 3Dは
2D, 3D, and 3D...
交われば最強バーチャルリアル
When they intersect, they're the ultimate virtual reality!
チュチュ チュチュチュ チュチュ
Chu chu, chu chu chu, chu chu!
イェーイ
Yeah!
僕らが見ている太陽って
The sun that we are looking at...
8分前の景色で
...is a scenery from eight minutes ago,
実はちょっと昔らしい
and is actually from a bit in the past.
そう考えると不思議かもね
It's kind of mysterious when you think about it.
そこにあるようでいて
It seems to be right there,
少しずれた時間を過ごしてる
but we're spending slightly out-of-sync time.
きっと僕らのコンセント
Surely, our outlet...
隣の人のことを
...doesn't know a single thing
1つも知らないけど
about the person next to us,
わからないまま 陽が沈む方へ向かった
but we headed toward the sunset without knowing.
アマテラス その手で触れて
Amateras, touch me with that hand...
輪になって踊りましょう
...and let's dance in a circle.
アマテラス 聴かせて あのね
Amateras, let me hear you say...
君だって歌えるよ
...that you can sing too.
誰にだって降り注いだ
The light from eight minutes ago...
8分前の光が射す方へ
...that poured down on everyone shines the way.
僕らは分かり合えない
We cannot fully understand each other,
お互いの世界には
and in our respective worlds,
誰も価値をつけられない
no one can put a value on them.
それでも隣で生きていたい
Even so, I want to live by your side.
こんなに狭い星だから
Since it's such a tiny planet,
肩でも組んでさ 歌いましょう
let's link our shoulders and sing.
ずっと一人ぼっちはもう最後
This is finally the end of being all alone.
岩のように厚い雲を
The clouds as thick as boulders...
こっそりとのぞいた手を握って
...I held the hand that peeked through secretly,
掴んで 引っ張り出して
grabbed it, and pulled it out!
アマテラス 照らす光は
Amateras, the light that shines...
寂しい記憶も同じように
...illuminates our lonely memories in the same way.
甘すぎず照らしたから
Because it shone without being too sweet,
背中を向けないで 進むだけ
I'll just move forward without turning my back.
アマテラス その手で触れて
Amateras, touch me with that hand...
輪になって踊りましょう
...and let's dance in a circle.
アマテラス 聴かせて あのね
Amateras, let me hear you say...
君だって歌えるよ
...that you can sing too.
世界中のどんな朝も
Every morning all over the world...
8分前の光に満ちている
...is filled with the light from eight minutes ago.
おーきどーき 返事はいいけど
Okey-dokey, your reply is good,
冗談なら笑えないよ
but if it's a joke, I can't laugh.
渋滞 曖昧 どっちを向いちゃうの
Traffic jam, ambiguity—which way should I face?
蜃気楼に手を伸ばした
I reached my hand out to the mirage.
微熱のような 夢物語
A dream-like story, like a slight fever.
そんな光は Midnight Flight
That kind of light is a midnight flight,...
画面の向こう
...on the other side of the screen.
まだ行かないで
Don't go yet,
幻じゃやだよ
I don't want it to be an illusion!
私を奪って
Take me away!
魅惑の Dancing Dancing Night
A captivating dancing, dancing night.
広がって 収まらない Universe
An expanding, uncontrollable universe.
君の言動は 私のシラバスを
Your words and actions are so stimulating...
書き換えちゃうほど刺激的 夢中だね
...they rewrite my syllabus. I'm so obsessed!
一切合切 ダンダンダン
Everything, absolutely everything, bang, bang, bang!
3・2・1で Dancing, Dancing
With 3, 2, 1, dancing, dancing!
夢中になって 絡み合う
Getting obsessed and intertwining.
Keep on dancing, my beat
Come on, we can dance, dance, dance, dance, dance...
声は闇に焼けたまま
My voice remains burnt in the darkness
目を覚ましても離れないで
Even if I open my eyes, please don't leave me
Maybe, needy, darling
お気に入りじゃないのよ
I'm not your favorite, am I?
太陽が忘れられない
But I can't forget the sun
誰彼それじゃないから
Because it's not just anyone
独り占めして euphoria
Monopolize me and feel the euphoria
気にしてないよな
You probably don't even care
言葉は装飾で
My words are so plain
メイクのようには流せない
I can't wash them away like makeup
360度偽りだって
Even if it's 360 degrees of lies
鑑飾できるよな
You can still identify it, right?
私にかまって
Pay attention to me
We are crazy, crazy love
待って、ロジカルにすればストーリー
Wait, logically speaking, it's a story
君の鼓動は
Your heartbeat is...
私の深層シンフォニーを
...playing my deep-soul symphony
繰り返すのよ センシティブ・ラインね
Repeating it, it's a sensitive line, isn't it?
過ぎ去ったネオン 残像上昇中ストーリー
A story of rising afterimages and neon lights of the past
Darling, 未来に漂えば
Darling, if I drift into the future
こぼれ落ちた
...and spill over...
指先でまた君を探している
I'll search for you again with my fingertips
その声を聞かせてよ
Please let me hear your voice
私にかまって
Pay attention to me
教えてよ恋の先を
And tell me what lies beyond love
広がった幼いマイユニバース
My expanding, childish universe
君の存在は
Your existence is...
私の脳内満天のスター
...the star filling the night sky of my mind
飛び込んだのよ 突き抜けてね
I jumped in, so break on through, okay?
いったいぜんたい dance, dance, dance, dance...
What on earth? Dance, dance, dance...
dance, dance, dance, dance, dance...
声は闇に焼けたまま
My voice remains burnt in the darkness
目を覚ましても離れないで
Even if I open my eyes, please don't leave me
ここに宣言します セブンスバウします
I hereby declare, I make the seven vows
開演までしばらくお待ちください。
[Please wait a moment for the performance to begin.]
ひとつ、病めるときも 健やかなるときも ずっと
First: whether in sickness or in health, always...
愛を歌い続けることを 堂々と誓います
...I proudly swear to keep singing of love.
ふたつ、歌うことも ダンスももっと 追求します
Second: I will pursue singing and dancing even more.
みっつ、ずっと推してもらえる アイドルになってみせます
Third: I will show you I can be an idol you'll support forever.
よっつ、不安な未来も 私が照らすんだ
Fourth: I will light up even the uncertain future.
それでも落ち込んじゃう日は
Even so, on days when I feel down...
思い出しているよ みんなのその笑顔
...I'll remember all of your smiles.
2026.01.10 Tokyo International Forum
January 10, 2026 at Tokyo International Forum
1st year 2019
2nd year 2020
3rd year 2021
4th year 2022
5th year 2023
6th year 2024
7th year 2025
with DJ ANKIMO
Are You Ready?
Dream in Motion New Year's Party 2026
未完成の地図を 輝きに変えて
Turning an incomplete map into brilliance,
誰にも真似できない
no one else can copy,
足跡を見せて
show me your footprints!
みんなー！
Everyone!
走り出した願いは 加速してくスピード
The wishes that started running are accelerating in speed.
目に映るものに 戸惑うなら
If you are bewildered by what meets your eyes...
仮想世界だって 私は見えてるでしょ
...even in a virtual world, you can see me, right?
君だけにリアルな 世界が世界
A world that is real only to you is the world.
時々不安で 泣き出そうにもなるよ
Sometimes I feel anxious and want to cry,
だけどドキドキが 嬉しくて ほら行くから
but this excitement is so wonderful, so here I go!
大きく手を叩いて
Clap your hands out loud!
君に届けたいよ
I want to reach you!
笑顔になって
With a smile on your face,
未来を見に行こうよ
let's go see the future!
負けないように願って 光を照らし合って
Wishing not to lose, shining our lights on each other,
平気だよ 一緒に笑いたいから
it's going to be okay, because I want to laugh with you.
綺麗になって ちょっぴり自信持って
Becoming beautiful, holding a little bit of confidence.
目と目合って ここで歌いたいの
Eye to eye, I want to sing here.
いつもよりもちょっと 大きな声でもっと
With a voice slightly louder than usual, even more,
君に届くように 歌ってほしいからだよ ねぇ
so that it reaches you... because I want you to sing, okay?
声がちょっとちっちゃいかも！
Your voices might be a bit too quiet!
スポットライトもうちょっと 当てていきたい最高潮
I want to shine the spotlight a little more at this climax.
不安も全部巻き込んで上がるステージで
Involving all my anxiety on this rising stage.
おしとやかになって これが私のロール
Becoming graceful, this is my role.
君だけに見せたい 二人だけの世界
I want to show only you a world of just the two of us.
みんな声出せるかー！
Can everyone make some noise?!
せーの、ワン、ツー！
One, two!
そうだ だけどさ 一緒に泣いてもいいよ
Yes, but you know, it's okay to cry together.
だけど明日になれば 明るい日がきっと来るから 準備して
But when tomorrow comes, a bright day will surely arrive, so get ready...
ねー！
Hey!
大きく歌って 歌って 君に届けたいよ
Sing out loud, sing, I want to reach you!
笑顔になって なって 未来を見に行こうよ
Put on a smile, smile, let's go see the future!
止まらない雨だって 風が向かい風だって
Even if the rain won't stop, even if the wind is a headwind,
私たちを彩る スパイスだから
they are the spices that color our lives.
綺麗になって なって ちょっと自信持って
Become beautiful, beautiful, with a little more confidence,
デタラメだって いいよ 君と一緒に 歌いたいよ保存
even if it's nonsense, that's fine, I want to sing together with you!
いつものようにもっと 誰よりも思い出に保存
Just like always, even more, let's make a memory more than anyone else,
響くだけじゃなく今 魔法をかけるよ さあ
not just echoing, but now I will cast a spell, come on!
さあ！
Come on!
せーの！もっと！もっと！
Ready, set, go! More! More!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
一つ、二つ、スイッチオンして またまた、また、恋に落ちてく
One, two, switch on, and again, again, again, falling in love...
落ちる、落ちる、私はそんな恋をするのだろう
Falling, falling, will I fall in love like that?
一瞬の視線に 走るシルエット 見え隠れした その衣装
In a fleeting glance, a running silhouette, that outfit appearing and disappearing...
Ah 恋に焦がれた 悪い、悪い子になれ
Ah, yearning for love, become a bad, bad child.
ゆらゆら、ゆら、開始の合図 グルグル回れ 映画館のよう
Swaying, swaying, swaying, the signal to start, spin round and round like a movie theater.
熱くなるまで 踊りましょう 秘密にするから保存
Let's dance until we get hot, since I'll keep it a secret...
もっと頂戴
Give me more!
キミとFallin' Rollin' Coaster 負けないで 揺れるココロ 縦に揺らす
With you, Fallin' Rollin' Coaster, don't lose, shaking my trembling heart vertically.
キミの隣 立って 負けないで ドキドキの恋しようよ
Standing next to you, don't lose, let's have a heart-pounding love!
どっちでしょう？ 吐息のくちづけ みんな どっちがいいかな？
Which one is it? A sighing kiss, everyone, which one is better?
キミには内緒 優しい魔法もほら
It's a secret from you, look, even the gentle magic...
いない いない ばぁ って? 今日もまた 遊びましょう
Peek-a-boo? Let's play again today.
魔法をかけて 恋の予感 瞳の奥で 見てててててててて
Casting magic, premonition of love, look deep into my eyes-s-s-s-s...
たいの？ キミと居たいの コツコツと 恋の足音は
Want to? I want to be with you, clatter-clatter, the footsteps of love...
どうしよう、どうしたら、どうしよう 暗い暗い夜になるまで
What should I do, what if, what should I do, until the dark, dark night comes...
踊る道標 私の世界にようこそって
The dancing guidepost, saying "welcome to my world"...
ねえ、いいでしょう？
Hey, isn't it nice?
キミとFallin' Rollin' Coaster 負けないで 揺れるココロ 縦に揺らす
With you, Fallin' Rollin' Coaster, don't lose, shaking my trembling heart vertically.
キミの隣 立って 負けないで ドキドキの恋しようよ
Standing next to you, don't lose, let's have a heart-pounding love!
どっちでしょう？ 吐息のくちづけ みんな どっちがいいかな？
Which one is it? A sighing kiss, everyone, which one is better?
キミには内緒 優しい魔法もほら
It's a secret from you, look, even the gentle magic...
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
いらない 真実は 忘れさせてあげるから
I don't need the truth, because I'll make you forget it.
上手な駆け引きに そっと目を閉じたら
When you gently close your eyes to the clever tactics...
ねえ、ねえ、ねえ、ねえ、ねえ、ねえ...
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
キミとFallin' Rollin' Coaster 負けないで あれもこれも 全部全部
With you, Fallin' Rollin' Coaster, don't lose, all of this and that, everything, everything,
キミの隣 立って 負けないで いたずらな瞳で 始めましょうさあ
standing next to you, don't lose, let's begin with mischievous eyes, come on!
キミとFallin' Rollin' Coaster 負けないで 揺れるココロ 縦に揺らす
With you, Fallin' Rollin' Coaster, don't lose, shaking my trembling heart vertically.
キミの隣 立って 負けないで ドキドキの恋しようよ
Standing next to you, don't lose, let's have a heart-pounding love!
どっちでしょう？ 吐息のくちづけ みんな どっちがいいかな？
Which one is it? A sighing kiss, everyone, which one is better?
キミには内緒 優しい魔法もほら
It's a secret from you, look, even the gentle magic...
ドキドキの恋しようよ
Let's have a heart-pounding love!
おっきなおっきな 穴が空くほど見つめて
Staring so hard at you, I could pierce a big, big hole.
冗談なら笑えないわ
If it's a joke, it's not funny.
近づきあう２つの生命に
To the two lives drawing closer,
シンパシーを感じている
I feel a strange sympathy.
異次元のようさ 身体が
My body feels like it's in another dimension,
遠い光のようだったり
or like a distant light.
衝動的感情 まだ隠して
Still hiding these impulsive emotions,
ねえ 混ざりあう 宇宙の引力で
hey, with the merging gravity of the universe...
エイリアン わたしエイリアン
Alien, I am an alien,
あなたの心を惑わせる
and I'm here to bewilder your heart.
交ざりあう宇宙の引力で
With the merging gravity of the universe,
感じてる 高鳴る鼓動
I feel my heart racing.
エイリアン あなたのエイリアン
Alien, your alien,
触れあえば傷は戻らない
once we touch, the wounds will never heal.
未知との遭遇に惹き合わされて
Drawn together by a close encounter.
ハスハスハスハスハス
Hah, hah, hah, hah, hah,
スピリチュアルなこのままで
keeping things spiritual like this,
目を覚ましても 離れないで
even if I open my eyes, don't leave me.
ベイビー ユニークに愛して
Baby, love me uniquely,
少女じゃないの 太陽系はすぐに狭くなる
I'm not a little girl, the solar system will soon grow too small.
遠く 遠く 底じゃないから
Far, far away, because it's not the bottom,
ヒトリシズカに踊り合って
dancing together like a chloranthus flower.
気にしているのは
What I care about is
メカニカルな恋に流されない
not being swept away by a mechanical love.
３、２、１
3, 2, 1...
酸欠気味になるほど
To the point of being nearly breathless,
酸素吸入器を頂戴よ
please give me an oxygen inhaler.
エイリアン わたしエイリアン
Alien, I am an alien,
あなたの心を惑わせる
and I'm here to bewilder your heart.
星屑クレイジー クレイジー ラブ
Stardust, crazy, crazy love,
果ての果てまで連れてって
take me to the very ends of the earth.
すれ違ったネオンサインをチューニングさ
Tuning the neon signs that passed each other by.
スライダーみたいに漂えば
If I drift like a slider,
抗う抗う間もなかった
I didn't even have time to resist.
波先で待った 君を探している
Waiting at the crest of the wave, I am looking for you.
その声を聞かせてよ
Let me hear that voice of yours.
エイリアン わたしエイリアン
Alien, I am an alien,
あなたの心を惑わせる
and I'm here to bewilder your heart.
交ざりあう宇宙の引力で
With the merging gravity of the universe,
感じてる 高鳴る鼓動
I feel my heart racing.
エイリアン あなたのエイリアン
Alien, your alien,
触れあえば傷は戻らない
once we touch, the wounds will never heal.
未知との遭遇に惹き合わされて
Drawn together by a close encounter.
ハスハスハスハスハス
Hah, hah, hah, hah, hah,
スピリチュアルなこのままで
keeping things spiritual like this,
目を覚ましても 離れないで
even if I open my eyes, don't leave me.
はーい！
Yeah!
皆さん、新年あけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year, everyone!
はーい！盛り上がってますか？
Yeah! Are you guys pumped up?
みんなで協力して、優しい気持ちでライブできてるかにゃ？
Is everyone cooperating and enjoying the live show with kind hearts?
いいね、素晴らしいよ。あはははは！
Great, that's wonderful. Ahahahaha!
みんな見えてるよ！
I can see all of you!
今日はみんな青いんだね。そっか、あれか、あのTシャツ。
Everyone is blue today. Ah, right, that T-shirt.
Tシャツが...今着てくれてる人？
The T-shirt... Is anyone wearing it right now?
おー、凄ーい！待って、当日券買ってくれた人っていますか？
Oh, awesome! Wait, is there anyone who bought same-day tickets?
おー、凄ーい！ありがとうございます！
Oh, awesome! Thank you so much!
凄ーい、感動した。ありがとうございます。本当に嬉しいです。
Amazing, I'm so touched. Thank you very much. I'm really happy.
ということで、ね。やりました。あれをやりましょうか。
With that said, yes. We did it. Shall we do that thing?
遠くから来てくれた人ー？
Anyone who came from far away?
そうだよね、飛行機とかできてくれた人いたもんね。
Right, because some people even flew here.
じゃあ、海外から来た人？
How about anyone from overseas?
じゃあ、声出さなくてもいい、あの、くるくるやるだけでもいいよ。
Well, you don't even have to shout, just waving it around is fine.
女の子ーー？
Any girls here?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
前のほうでぴょんぴょん飛んでるの見えたよ。
I saw you jumping up and down in the front.
めっちゃ爆笑してる！
You're laughing so hard!
奥のほうの子も見えてるよ。大きな声、ありがとうございました！
I can see you in the back, too. Thank you for your loud cheers!
そして、２階席ー！
And, the second floor balcony seats!
１階席ー！
First floor seats!
じゃ、またペンライトで遊んじゃおう。
Now, let's play with the penlights again.
左の人、緑ー！
People on the left, green!
右の人は、じゃあ、オレンジ！
Then, people on the right, orange!
じゃあ、真ん中は、青ー！
Then, the middle, blue!
おー、綺麗だー！
Oh, it's beautiful!
みんな、今回はね、こんな感じで
Everyone, this time, like this,
みんなも演出に参加しちゃうライブになっているよ！
you can all participate in the concert production!
みんなで楽しんでいこうね！
Let's all have fun together!
今日はみんなも主役なんだー！
Today, everyone is the main character!
美味しい、美味しい。美味しいから！
It's delicious, delicious. It really is delicious!
夜はね、いっぱい動くと思って、まあもう動いてるけど
I thought I'd be moving around a lot tonight—well, I already am—
昼から飲めばよかった。スポドリ一択！
so I should've been drinking this since noon. Sports drink is the only choice!
がっつり。今年の目標みたいに、ムキムキになっていこうと思います。
With a passion. Just like my goal for this year, I plan to get muscular.
というわけで、じゃあ、初めての人ー！
And so, next, those who are here for the first time!
おー。あ、これ、あ、拍手してくれて、ありがとうございます。
Oh. Ah, thank you all for clapping.
一番最初のライブから全部来てるよって人いる？
Is anyone here who has been to every single concert since the very first one?
おおー！ありがとうございます！
Ooh! Thank you very much!
というわけでね、みんな分かったね。はじめましての人も、
So everyone, you get it now, right? Whether you're here for the first time,
いつも、そらともじゃ、ない人も、そして昔から応援してる人、
whether you aren't usually a Soratomo, or whether you've supported me since way back,
みんな集まって、みんながすでにそらともだよ。みんな楽しく過ごしていこうね！
when we all gather, everyone is already a Soratomo! Let's all have a great time!
というわけで、なんと！
And with that, what do you know!
YouTubeでも無料配信...
The free broadcast on YouTube...
あ、まだ全部言ってないのに！
Ah, I haven't even finished saying it all yet!
ふふふ、ここね、まだ来たばっかり？まだ来たばっかりかと思うけど...
Fufu, you probably feel like you've only just arrived, but...
続きは、概要欄から、え、えー、えー、えー、いえーいの人はどうした？
the rest can be found from the description box... Wait, what's with the "yay" people?
これ、あ、配信会場の人も、楽しんでってねー！わーい！
Also, to those at the streaming venue, please enjoy the show as well! Yay!
それでは、もう一回飲んでから行くね。水分も大事。
Well then, I'll take one more drink before we go. Hydration is important, too.
助かる、助かってくれてありがとう！
Blessed? Thank you for being blessed!
では、次の曲も楽しんでいってね！
Now, please enjoy the next song too!
輪郭の無い月を見てる
Looking at the outline-less moon
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
[On-screen: The free preview broadcast ends here.]
The free introductory broadcast ends here.